[
    {
        "title": "Dozens dead in Ukrainian strike on Russian troops – Moscow",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569298-makeevka-strike-ukraine-casualties/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Makeyevka",
                44,
                53,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Donetsk People’s Republic",
                57,
                82,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Defense Ministry",
                84,
                104,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "More than 60",
                111,
                123,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                124,
                131,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                161,
                170,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                187,
                193,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Monday",
                207,
                213,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                272,
                279,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Donbass",
                290,
                297,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Makeyevka",
                328,
                337,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                341,
                347,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "six",
                387,
                390,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "US",
                405,
                407,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "HIMARS",
                417,
                423,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Defense ministry",
                451,
                471,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Two",
                479,
                482,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "four",
                533,
                537,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "63",
                563,
                565,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "the Donetsk People’s Republic’s Information",
                750,
                793,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Daniil Bezsonov",
                803,
                818,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "0:01 am",
                945,
                952,
                "TIME"
            ],
            [
                "New Year’s",
                956,
                966,
                "EVENT"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Goals outlined for Russia’s long-range air force in 2023",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569289-strategic-aviation-ukraine-kobylash/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Ukraine",
                55,
                62,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Sergey Kobylash",
                86,
                101,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                108,
                115,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                168,
                174,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                199,
                206,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2023",
                210,
                214,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Sergey Kobylash",
                285,
                300,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "this year",
                405,
                414,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kobylash",
                468,
                476,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Monday",
                486,
                492,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the Defense Ministry",
                506,
                526,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "2023",
                728,
                732,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Last month",
                959,
                969,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kobylash",
                971,
                979,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                989,
                996,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Krasnaya Zvezda",
                1014,
                1029,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1139,
                1146,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1149,
                1155,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "three",
                1284,
                1289,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Tu-95MS",
                1323,
                1330,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Tu-160",
                1335,
                1341,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the New Year",
                1420,
                1432,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "Two",
                1494,
                1497,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "One",
                1558,
                1561,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1671,
                1677,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Last month",
                1750,
                1760,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1762,
                1769,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "at least two",
                1775,
                1787,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                1866,
                1873,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Saratov",
                1888,
                1895,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "the Defense Ministry",
                1929,
                1949,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Soviet",
                1965,
                1971,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Engels",
                2009,
                2015,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Dyagilevo",
                2020,
                2029,
                "FAC"
            ],
            [
                "UAVs",
                2104,
                2108,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "six",
                2126,
                2129,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "one",
                2162,
                2165,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                2201,
                2204,
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Stoltenberg warns of potential new Russian offensive in Ukraine",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569287-stoltenberg-russian-offensive-ukraine/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Kiev",
                21,
                25,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "NATO",
                51,
                55,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "West",
                84,
                88,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                138,
                145,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                150,
                156,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "NATO",
                158,
                162,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Jens Stoltenberg",
                181,
                197,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Sunday",
                206,
                212,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                247,
                251,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Stoltenberg",
                268,
                279,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "BBC",
                289,
                292,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                298,
                304,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "September",
                341,
                350,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                363,
                369,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "US",
                571,
                573,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "West",
                615,
                619,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                676,
                683,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                754,
                760,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                828,
                835,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Europe",
                873,
                879,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                913,
                920,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Friday",
                1026,
                1032,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Stoltenberg",
                1034,
                1045,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1122,
                1129,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1186,
                1192,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "late February",
                1217,
                1230,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1292,
                1299,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                1335,
                1341,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Last month",
                1343,
                1353,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                1355,
                1362,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Vladimir Putin",
                1373,
                1387,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "NATO",
                1400,
                1404,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                1481,
                1487,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1491,
                1498,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                1553,
                1560,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1597,
                1604,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "West",
                1656,
                1660,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1672,
                1679,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1761,
                1767,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kremlin",
                1793,
                1800,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1836,
                1843,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1854,
                1858,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                1894,
                1900,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1919,
                1923,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Donetsk",
                2034,
                2041,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Lugansk",
                2043,
                2050,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kherson",
                2052,
                2059,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zaporozhye",
                2064,
                2074,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                2087,
                2093,
                "GPE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ukrainian drone hits energy facility inside Russia – governor",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569285-ukraine-drone-bryansk-fire/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Bryansk Region",
                16,
                30,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Aleksandr Bogomaz",
                70,
                87,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                96,
                105,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                141,
                147,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Monday",
                174,
                180,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Aleksandr Bogomaz",
                231,
                248,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Klimovsky",
                289,
                298,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                324,
                330,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Bogomaz",
                347,
                354,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Telegram",
                364,
                372,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Bogomaz",
                679,
                686,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                797,
                803,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                828,
                835,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "late February",
                839,
                852,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                854,
                858,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                926,
                933,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Bryansk",
                952,
                959,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Belgorod",
                961,
                969,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Kursk",
                974,
                979,
                "PRODUCT"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Zelensky aide moots ‘Lord of the Rings’ concept to win conflict",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569284-ukraine-lord-of-the-rings-monarchy/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Ukraine",
                0,
                7,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Return of the King",
                62,
                80,
                "WORK_OF_ART"
            ],
            [
                "Alexey Arestovich",
                83,
                100,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                111,
                118,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                162,
                168,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Vladimir Zelensky",
                197,
                214,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                256,
                260,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "J.R.R. Tolkien's",
                264,
                280,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Alexey Arestovich",
                322,
                339,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Rings",
                465,
                470,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                534,
                541,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                599,
                608,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Oleg Skripka",
                618,
                630,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Sunday",
                634,
                640,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                746,
                752,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Zelensky’s",
                799,
                809,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Arestovich",
                878,
                888,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                926,
                933,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kievan Rus",
                1016,
                1026,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "the 9th century",
                1032,
                1047,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kievan Rus",
                1071,
                1081,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "four centuries later",
                1082,
                1102,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ruriks",
                1108,
                1114,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Grand Duchy of Moscow",
                1121,
                1146,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Tsardom of Russia",
                1216,
                1237,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the United Kingdom",
                1282,
                1300,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Arestovich",
                1500,
                1510,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Rings",
                1535,
                1540,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Commonwealth of Independent States",
                1632,
                1670,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "St. Petersburg",
                1680,
                1694,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "last month",
                1713,
                1723,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "nine",
                1772,
                1776,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Tolkien",
                1817,
                1824,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Kremlin Press",
                1976,
                1989,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Dmitry Peskov",
                2000,
                2013,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "New Year’s",
                2055,
                2065,
                "EVENT"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Russia celebrates New Year (PHOTOS)",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569259-new-year-celebrations-moscow/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Russians",
                61,
                69,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "11",
                77,
                79,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2023",
                108,
                112,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Four thousand",
                196,
                209,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                245,
                251,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Christmas",
                269,
                278,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Red Square",
                289,
                299,
                "FAC"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                442,
                449,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                467,
                473,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "St. Petersburg",
                478,
                492,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                729,
                736,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "second",
                753,
                759,
                "ORDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "St. Petersburg",
                774,
                788,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "New Year’s Eve",
                906,
                920,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "Chita",
                1014,
                1019,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1023,
                1029,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Far East",
                1032,
                1040,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1096,
                1102,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1127,
                1134,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "New Year",
                1137,
                1145,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "the People’s Republic of Donetsk",
                1178,
                1210,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Lugansk",
                1215,
                1222,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "LPR",
                1232,
                1235,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Zaporozhye",
                1249,
                1259,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Kherson",
                1264,
                1271,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "the Russian Federation",
                1294,
                1316,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "autumn",
                1320,
                1326,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Mariupol",
                1380,
                1388,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the first months",
                1418,
                1434,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Lugansk",
                1459,
                1466,
                "GPE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ukraine kills and injures Donbass civilians – officials",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569264-donbass-civilians-ukrainian-shelling/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "New Year",
                49,
                57,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "Donetsk",
                84,
                91,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Lugansk",
                148,
                155,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "LPR",
                157,
                160,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                230,
                234,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "overnight",
                242,
                251,
                "TIME"
            ],
            [
                "the day",
                370,
                377,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                388,
                397,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "155mm",
                413,
                418,
                "QUANTITY"
            ],
            [
                "NATO",
                419,
                423,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Three",
                491,
                496,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "three-months-old",
                517,
                533,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Donetsk’s",
                579,
                588,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Alexey Kulemzin",
                624,
                639,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Sunday",
                652,
                658,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "More than 15",
                661,
                673,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Makeevka",
                727,
                735,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "24-hour",
                880,
                887,
                "TIME"
            ],
            [
                "At least six",
                929,
                941,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                971,
                980,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "LPR",
                1044,
                1047,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Tatyana Kovalyeva",
                1088,
                1105,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "RIA Novosti",
                1112,
                1123,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "three",
                1169,
                1174,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "some 30 minutes",
                1200,
                1215,
                "TIME"
            ],
            [
                "first",
                1291,
                1296,
                "ORDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "At least six",
                1311,
                1323,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Kovalyeva",
                1415,
                1424,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Donbass",
                1448,
                1455,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1528,
                1532,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1566,
                1572,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1577,
                1584,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "more than 1,000",
                1591,
                1606,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "last year",
                1627,
                1636,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "DPR",
                1644,
                1647,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the New Year's Eve",
                1729,
                1747,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1768,
                1772,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Donbass",
                1807,
                1814,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                1820,
                1827,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1887,
                1894,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "The Russian Defense Ministry",
                1897,
                1925,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Sunday",
                1934,
                1940,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                2039,
                2043,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                2093,
                2099,
                "GPE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ukrainian drone depots destroyed – Moscow",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569262-drone-attack-military-strike/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "UAVs",
                57,
                61,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Russian Defense Ministry",
                63,
                91,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                129,
                136,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                167,
                174,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                186,
                192,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Defense Ministry",
                195,
                211,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Sunday",
                220,
                226,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                251,
                260,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                322,
                326,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                368,
                374,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                408,
                415,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                570,
                574,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                622,
                628,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                702,
                709,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Telegram",
                749,
                757,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "20",
                763,
                765,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Saturday",
                808,
                816,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                822,
                828,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "12",
                892,
                894,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                935,
                944,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                960,
                964,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Vitaly Klitschko",
                971,
                987,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "one",
                993,
                996,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "20",
                1019,
                1021,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Nikolaev",
                1103,
                1111,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Khmelnitsky",
                1116,
                1127,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "December 5",
                1165,
                1175,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1177,
                1184,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                1216,
                1222,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Saratov",
                1251,
                1258,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                1291,
                1298,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "the Defense Ministry",
                1323,
                1343,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Soviet",
                1359,
                1365,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Engels",
                1410,
                1416,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Dyagilevo",
                1421,
                1430,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "air defenses",
                1455,
                1467,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "three",
                1503,
                1508,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                1551,
                1554,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Engels airfield",
                1595,
                1610,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1634,
                1638,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "December 23",
                1642,
                1653,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "UAV",
                1659,
                1662,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "three",
                1687,
                1692,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                1756,
                1763,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1849,
                1856,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1900,
                1906,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Crimea",
                1928,
                1934,
                "ORG"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Putin gives unusual New Year address",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569238-putin-new-year-ukraine/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Russia",
                0,
                6,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "years-long",
                30,
                40,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                94,
                101,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Vladimir Putin",
                112,
                126,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "New Year's Eve",
                153,
                167,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "Saturday",
                179,
                187,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the past year",
                260,
                273,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kremlin",
                368,
                375,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Putin",
                424,
                429,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "this year",
                430,
                439,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "annual",
                454,
                460,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the Southern Military District",
                472,
                502,
                "FAC"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                706,
                713,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "February",
                764,
                772,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                810,
                816,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                999,
                1006,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1127,
                1133,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "today",
                1194,
                1199,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "New Year",
                1238,
                1246,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "the outgoing year",
                1330,
                1347,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1500,
                1506,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "a year",
                1600,
                1606,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "today",
                1742,
                1747,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the Russian Federation",
                1832,
                1854,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "four",
                1896,
                1900,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1947,
                1953,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "September",
                1960,
                1969,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1993,
                1999,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the past year",
                2060,
                2073,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Putin",
                2075,
                2080,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                2119,
                2125,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                2178,
                2185,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                2374,
                2380,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Crimea",
                2433,
                2439,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2014",
                2443,
                2447,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "this year",
                2453,
                2462,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Putin",
                2641,
                2646,
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Russian soldiers released from Ukrainian captivity – Defense Ministry",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569239-prisoner-swap-russia-ukraine/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Moscow",
                42,
                48,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                110,
                117,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                148,
                152,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "New Year’s Eve",
                179,
                193,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "Defense Ministry",
                237,
                253,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Saturday",
                282,
                290,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Telegram",
                377,
                385,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russian Aerospace Forces",
                389,
                413,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                466,
                472,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Russian Defense Ministry",
                533,
                561,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Donetsk People’s Republic",
                690,
                719,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Denis Pushilin",
                721,
                735,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Telegram",
                745,
                753,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                800,
                806,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                811,
                818,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "82",
                829,
                831,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Saturday",
                866,
                874,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                876,
                880,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Andrey Yermak",
                918,
                931,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                952,
                961,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Vladimir Zelensky",
                972,
                989,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "140",
                992,
                995,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "82",
                1034,
                1036,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "132",
                1081,
                1084,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "eight",
                1093,
                1098,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "22",
                1106,
                1108,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "118",
                1122,
                1125,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Saturday",
                1192,
                1200,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "third this month",
                1218,
                1234,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                1278,
                1285,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "December 6",
                1298,
                1308,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "60",
                1315,
                1317,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "50",
                1349,
                1351,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1371,
                1380,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "December 1",
                1394,
                1404,
                "DATE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Kiev mayor criticizes Ukrainian authorities",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569230-kiev-mayor-criticizes-government-preparedness/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Russia",
                61,
                67,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Vitaly Klitschko",
                81,
                97,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "German",
                109,
                115,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev Vitaly Klitschko",
                136,
                157,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                175,
                184,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                238,
                245,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "early 2022",
                268,
                278,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Der Spiegel",
                298,
                309,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "German",
                432,
                438,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Friday",
                465,
                471,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Klitschko",
                473,
                482,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                571,
                578,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                679,
                685,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "late February",
                721,
                734,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                885,
                894,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Western",
                928,
                935,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                940,
                949,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "late 2021",
                1030,
                1039,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1045,
                1054,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Russians",
                1104,
                1112,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1126,
                1130,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Klitschko",
                1132,
                1141,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1231,
                1240,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "the first 24 hours",
                1256,
                1274,
                "TIME"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                1282,
                1289,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1495,
                1501,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1519,
                1526,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "February 24",
                1530,
                1541,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1550,
                1554,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                1582,
                1587,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1663,
                1672,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Germany",
                1707,
                1714,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "France",
                1719,
                1725,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2014",
                1748,
                1752,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1761,
                1770,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Pyotr Poroshenko",
                1781,
                1797,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1822,
                1826,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "February 2022",
                1916,
                1929,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kremlin",
                1935,
                1942,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Donbass",
                1958,
                1965,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                2016,
                2023,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Western",
                2093,
                2100,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "September",
                2119,
                2128,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Lugansk",
                2142,
                2149,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kherson",
                2162,
                2169,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zaporozhye Regions",
                2174,
                2192,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                2217,
                2223,
                "GPE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Confessions by Hollande and Merkel are ‘formalization of betrayal’ – top Russian senator",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569222-hollande-merkel-minsk-ukraine/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "West",
                4,
                8,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                53,
                60,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Konstantin Kosachev",
                74,
                93,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Thousands",
                100,
                109,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                153,
                160,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2014",
                167,
                171,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "West",
                184,
                188,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                201,
                206,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                254,
                260,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Saturday",
                297,
                305,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Konstantin Kosachev",
                316,
                335,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "French",
                375,
                381,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Francois Hollande",
                392,
                409,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                419,
                424,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                477,
                481,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                554,
                561,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                591,
                597,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "German",
                695,
                701,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Angela Merkel",
                713,
                726,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                746,
                751,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "December",
                763,
                771,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                795,
                802,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2014",
                885,
                889,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "2015",
                894,
                898,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Germany",
                922,
                929,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "France",
                931,
                937,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                942,
                948,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1003,
                1007,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "the People’s Republics of Donetsk",
                1012,
                1045,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Lugansk",
                1050,
                1057,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1099,
                1108,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1116,
                1120,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                1202,
                1208,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "February 24",
                1245,
                1256,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1303,
                1310,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kosachev",
                1458,
                1466,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Telegram",
                1476,
                1484,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "European",
                1533,
                1541,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "UK",
                1642,
                1644,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Spain",
                1649,
                1654,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Scotland",
                1701,
                1709,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Catalonia",
                1714,
                1723,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Merkel and Hollande",
                1770,
                1789,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "thousands",
                1853,
                1862,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "the past eight years",
                1888,
                1908,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1925,
                1932,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "West",
                1957,
                1961,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                1990,
                1995,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Kosachev",
                2024,
                2032,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "UN",
                2058,
                2060,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "more than 14,000",
                2072,
                2088,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Donbass",
                2111,
                2118,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "between 2014 and early 2022",
                2119,
                2146,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                2175,
                2180,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                2239,
                2245,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                2268,
                2274,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                2389,
                2394,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "The People’s Republic of Donetsk",
                2415,
                2447,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Zaporozhye",
                2472,
                2482,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Kherson",
                2487,
                2494,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                2515,
                2522,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "autumn",
                2532,
                2538,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                2566,
                2570,
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Donetsk reveals number of civilians killed in 2022",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569211-donetsk-civilian-casualties-number/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Russian",
                22,
                29,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "1,000",
                46,
                51,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "this year",
                52,
                61,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Some 1,091",
                87,
                97,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "more than 3,500",
                124,
                139,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "2022",
                151,
                155,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the Donetsk People’s Republic",
                188,
                217,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Friday",
                269,
                275,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "DPR",
                314,
                317,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                367,
                374,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "2014",
                383,
                387,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "5,441",
                400,
                405,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "the past year",
                436,
                449,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                455,
                464,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Donetsk",
                511,
                518,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                783,
                792,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "DPR",
                902,
                905,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Darya Morozova",
                921,
                935,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                979,
                983,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Morozova",
                1112,
                1120,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Donbass",
                1182,
                1189,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                1349,
                1355,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1360,
                1364,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1367,
                1373,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1391,
                1398,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "February 24",
                1402,
                1413,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1422,
                1426,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                1454,
                1459,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Germany",
                1484,
                1491,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "France",
                1496,
                1502,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Donetsk",
                1540,
                1547,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1586,
                1595,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1610,
                1619,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Pyotr Poroshenko",
                1630,
                1646,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1671,
                1675,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "2014",
                1703,
                1707,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "German",
                1815,
                1821,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Angela Merkel",
                1833,
                1846,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "French",
                1851,
                1857,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Francois Hollande",
                1868,
                1885,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                1918,
                1923,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                2019,
                2026,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                2048,
                2054,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                2068,
                2075,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Western",
                2145,
                2152,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                2168,
                2172,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                2185,
                2192,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "September",
                2234,
                2243,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "four",
                2245,
                2249,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                2259,
                2268,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "DPR",
                2282,
                2285,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Lugansk People’s Republic",
                2290,
                2319,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "LPR",
                2321,
                2324,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Kherson",
                2338,
                2345,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zaporozhye",
                2350,
                2360,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                2395,
                2401,
                "GPE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Ukraine is ‘first multipolar’ conflict – Dugin",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569213-dugin-ukraine-multipolar-war/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "West",
                4,
                8,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                58,
                65,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                104,
                111,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "first",
                128,
                133,
                "ORDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                160,
                166,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "West",
                248,
                252,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "totalitarian",
                276,
                288,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Aleksandr Dugin",
                310,
                325,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "RT",
                331,
                333,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Friday",
                363,
                369,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "West",
                406,
                410,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Dugin",
                421,
                426,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "West",
                463,
                467,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Russophobia",
                559,
                570,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                585,
                591,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Cold War",
                619,
                627,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "the Soviet Union",
                723,
                739,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "December 1991",
                759,
                772,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Dugin",
                849,
                854,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "one",
                938,
                941,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                949,
                952,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "one",
                958,
                961,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "West",
                1074,
                1078,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "Western",
                1221,
                1228,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "RT’s",
                1263,
                1267,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Donald Courter",
                1268,
                1282,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1515,
                1521,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "centuries",
                1553,
                1562,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Western",
                1708,
                1715,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1919,
                1925,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Dugin",
                2090,
                2095,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "RT",
                2101,
                2103,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "December 1991",
                2125,
                2138,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the Soviet Union",
                2151,
                2167,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                2230,
                2236,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                2248,
                2255,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Vladimir Putin",
                2266,
                2280,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Sea Power",
                2371,
                2380,
                "WORK_OF_ART"
            ],
            [
                "USSR",
                2393,
                2397,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Russian Empire",
                2424,
                2442,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                2505,
                2508,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "English",
                2560,
                2567,
                "LANGUAGE"
            ],
            [
                "Harold Mackinder",
                2579,
                2595,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Heartland",
                2620,
                2629,
                "LOC"
            ],
            [
                "60-year-old",
                2700,
                2711,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Kremlin",
                2773,
                2780,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                2848,
                2855,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Western",
                2892,
                2899,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                2931,
                2938,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Dugin",
                2953,
                2958,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Darya",
                2970,
                2975,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "29",
                2977,
                2979,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "August",
                3001,
                3007,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                3033,
                3042,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                3058,
                3062,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "US",
                3089,
                3091,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                3154,
                3163,
                "NORP"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Co-founder of Russia's largest IT company says goodbye",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569199-yandex-founder-farewell-message/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Arkady Volozh",
                11,
                24,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arkady Volozh",
                66,
                79,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                99,
                106,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Yandex",
                122,
                128,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Friday",
                171,
                177,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "EU",
                291,
                293,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Yandex’s",
                345,
                353,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                354,
                361,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Volozh",
                466,
                472,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Yandex",
                494,
                500,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "TASS",
                519,
                523,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "recent months",
                555,
                568,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "New Year’s",
                599,
                609,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "Yandex",
                667,
                673,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "these 30 years",
                729,
                743,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                958,
                964,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Yandex",
                969,
                975,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "RIA Novosti",
                996,
                1007,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Volozh",
                1013,
                1019,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "November",
                1107,
                1115,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Alexey Kudrin",
                1143,
                1156,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1158,
                1164,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1316,
                1322,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1357,
                1363,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Soviet",
                1381,
                1387,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Volozh",
                1610,
                1616,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Reuters",
                1763,
                1770,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Dutch",
                1781,
                1786,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "the Yandex Group",
                1872,
                1888,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                1982,
                1989,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Yandex",
                2017,
                2023,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "edtech",
                2144,
                2150,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                2228,
                2234,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Volozh",
                2236,
                2242,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "four",
                2298,
                2302,
                "CARDINAL"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Russia beefs up strategic aviation (VIDEO)",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569188-strategic-aviation-new-bombers/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "One",
                0,
                3,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                109,
                115,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                216,
                219,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Tu-160M",
                220,
                227,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "United Aircraft Corporation",
                287,
                314,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Friday",
                334,
                340,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "UAC",
                424,
                427,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Soviet-era",
                586,
                596,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the 1970s",
                647,
                656,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the M3M",
                734,
                741,
                "PRODUCT"
            ],
            [
                "2018",
                760,
                764,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                802,
                805,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Tu-160M",
                806,
                813,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "One",
                856,
                859,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                977,
                983,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Tu-160",
                1062,
                1068,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1099,
                1105,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Sergey Chemezov",
                1251,
                1266,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Rostec",
                1280,
                1286,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UAC",
                1292,
                1295,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "UAC",
                1327,
                1330,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Tu-160",
                1431,
                1437,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the late 1980s",
                1488,
                1502,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the Soviet Union",
                1558,
                1574,
                "GPE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Russia ‘extremely concerned’ over Ukrainian missile in Belarus",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569187-kremlin-belarus-ukrainian-missile/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Moscow",
                0,
                6,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                11,
                16,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kremlin",
                77,
                84,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Belarusian",
                112,
                122,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                137,
                146,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Kremlin",
                186,
                193,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Dmitry Peskov",
                205,
                218,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Friday",
                239,
                245,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Belarus",
                255,
                262,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                270,
                276,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                297,
                300,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                515,
                520,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                604,
                608,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Thursday",
                614,
                622,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Belarusian",
                628,
                638,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                716,
                723,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "S-300",
                751,
                756,
                "PRODUCT"
            ],
            [
                "Kirill Kazantsev",
                808,
                824,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Belarusian",
                830,
                840,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                876,
                881,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "S-300",
                975,
                980,
                "PRODUCT"
            ],
            [
                "Belarus",
                1068,
                1075,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1102,
                1108,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukraine",
                1185,
                1192,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                1233,
                1237,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Belarusian",
                1255,
                1265,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Belarus",
                1324,
                1331,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1378,
                1387,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                1446,
                1449,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Minsk",
                1459,
                1464,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Western",
                1556,
                1563,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1587,
                1596,
                "NORP"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Over 3,000 bodies of civilians recovered in Mariupol – investigators",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569180-mariupol-civilian-deaths-ukraine/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Russian",
                0,
                7,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                39,
                48,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                141,
                150,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Mariupol",
                180,
                188,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "thousands",
                201,
                210,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                231,
                238,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "3,000",
                316,
                321,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Kiev",
                368,
                372,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                473,
                479,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Investigative Committee",
                482,
                505,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Friday",
                509,
                515,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Aleksandr Bastrykin",
                539,
                558,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mariupol",
                577,
                585,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                623,
                632,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Donetsk People’s Republic",
                668,
                697,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "February",
                734,
                742,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "May",
                747,
                750,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                755,
                764,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                806,
                813,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "DPR",
                818,
                821,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                830,
                836,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                914,
                923,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                976,
                983,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1119,
                1128,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "April",
                1215,
                1220,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "51",
                1242,
                1244,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1298,
                1307,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "3,000",
                1379,
                1384,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1417,
                1423,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                1554,
                1563,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Valery Zaluzhny",
                1605,
                1620,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "the Investigative Committee",
                1675,
                1702,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Mariupol",
                2025,
                2033,
                "GPE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Putin invites Xi for state visit",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569184-putin-invites-xi-state-visit/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "Russia",
                0,
                6,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Chinese",
                33,
                40,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "next spring",
                48,
                59,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                89,
                96,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Chinese",
                129,
                136,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                155,
                161,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "next year",
                162,
                171,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Vladimir Putin",
                173,
                187,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Friday",
                249,
                255,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Putin",
                282,
                287,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Xi",
                306,
                308,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "next year",
                407,
                416,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Moscow",
                548,
                554,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the spring of next year",
                558,
                581,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Russian",
                612,
                619,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Xi",
                631,
                633,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Chinese-Russian",
                725,
                740,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "two",
                936,
                939,
                "CARDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "China",
                995,
                1000,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                1005,
                1011,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Putin",
                1062,
                1067,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Xi",
                1072,
                1074,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "2022",
                1098,
                1102,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "February",
                1107,
                1115,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "Putin",
                1117,
                1122,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Beijing",
                1131,
                1138,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Olympic",
                1150,
                1157,
                "EVENT"
            ],
            [
                "Chinese",
                1178,
                1185,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "September",
                1198,
                1207,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the Shanghai Cooperation Organisation",
                1248,
                1285,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Samarkand",
                1289,
                1298,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Uzbekistan",
                1300,
                1310,
                "GPE"
            ]
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Doomed to fail: How Lenin and Stalin placed a ticking time bomb under the Soviet Union exactly 100 years ago",
        "link": "https://www.rt.com/russia/569146-100-years-of-soviet-union/?utm_source=rss&utm_medium=rss&utm_campaign=RSS",
        "keywords": [
            [
                "USSR",
                4,
                8,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "100 years ago",
                89,
                102,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "December 30, 1922",
                107,
                124,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "First",
                183,
                188,
                "ORDINAL"
            ],
            [
                "Soviets",
                211,
                218,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "the Russian Soviet Federative Socialist Republic",
                239,
                287,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Ukrainian",
                301,
                310,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Soviet",
                311,
                317,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "SSR",
                338,
                341,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Belarusian SSR",
                347,
                361,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "the Transcaucasian Federation",
                367,
                396,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Declaration and Treaty on the Formation of the USSR",
                408,
                459,
                "WORK_OF_ART"
            ],
            [
                "Bolsheviks",
                521,
                531,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "1991",
                597,
                601,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "this day",
                606,
                614,
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "the Soviet Union",
                630,
                646,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Russia",
                681,
                687,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Soviet",
                703,
                709,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "Bolshevik",
                754,
                763,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "USSR",
                956,
                960,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Vladimir Lenin",
                1047,
                1061,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Joseph Stalin",
                1066,
                1079,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Lenin",
                1095,
                1100,
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "USSR",
                1122,
                1126,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "republics",
                1275,
                1284,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Communist",
                1505,
                1514,
                "NORP"
            ],
            [
                "USSR",
                1567,
                1571,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the Communist Party",
                1652,
                1671,
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "the Soviet Union",
                1723,
                1739,
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "the world proletariat",
                1864,
